i-dressup.com 2011-12-02

# Privacy policy - i-Dressup Dress up Games

**Privacy Policy**

To play games in I-Dressup.com you do not need to give up any personal information. 

When you register as a member at iZone, the community in I-Dressup, we collect Personal Information including your email address, first name, last name, and birthday, or any information that is voluntarily provided by you. 

We maintain log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. We do not link IP addresses to personal information. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on our Web sites and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of abuse, however, we may block certain IP addresses. 

**The way we use Personal Information**

Your email address is used by I-Dressup to send information about new services at I-Dressup. We will not sell your email address to any third party vendors. The information about age is mainly used to identify minors that need to get permission from their parents or legal guardian to become members at I-Dressup.com (Minors in the US are defined as children under 13, in non-US minors are defined as under 16 of age.) 

We reserve the right to collect and disclose (to our affiliates and to non-affiliate third parties) user behavior and Personal Information to the extent permitted by applicable law, as specifically restricted below or in the Terms of Use. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy or elsewhere, we reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law (including, without limitation, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), regulation, legal process, law enforcement requests, demands by parties claiming your infringement of their rights or governmental request, to edit, refuse to post or remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in our sole discretion; or to act in an emergency to protect someone's safety or legal rights. 

We have no control over third parties to whom you may give Personal Information through the use of I-Dressup.com. We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as email, search, advertising sales, ecommerce; completing an order; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. 

From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements to the I-Dressup services as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our services. 

We may also use personally identifiable user information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to users based on their demographic and behavioral information. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Opt-Out and Termination:**

We believe that our ability to share your Personal Information with our affiliates, vendors and certain third parties improves our ability to provide services to you. However, if you object to our sharing of your personal information and would like to exercise your rights under the Financial Services Modernization Act and the Fair Reporting Act to limit our use of certain information governed by the mandatory opt-out provisions of those acts (should we ever collect such information), and if you would like to terminate our use of your Personal Information on a going forward basis (except as it relates to prior financial transaction and communications) you can do that by contacting us. However, this will result in the termination of your I-Dressup user account(s). Please click here to contact us. 

**Cookie**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie enables us to collect information about your visits to I-Dressup. We may use this information to enhance your I-Dressup experience and may share some information with our members, vendors, sponsors or others. 

You can turn off the cookie function in your web browser, then you won't be able to register as a member or log in. 

**Parental rights**

As a parent you have the right to review your minor child's personal information, have it deleted and refuse I-Dressup to further collect information from your child. This would of course require a proper identification. Please contact us at parentsright@i-dressup.com   
(Minor in the US = under 13)   
(Minor in non-US= under 16)

**Google and DoubleClick DART cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
